Hi, and this is where some I will explain you what is smart actions of his Harvka powers
and how to use it. To see the type of example, let's open any file like button.jsx
and we will go through all the quick actions and I will show you some examples.
The first quick action we can use is rename symbols. It is useful when we want to rename
some variables. For example, we can select the variable variable, click do the right click,
and then choose rename symbol and click on the magic icons and compile it with just the names.
So let's choose the button text variable and you see do the renaming in all the file.
The next quick action you can use is explain code. We can choose this import, do the right click,
compile it, explain. You see it open at the chat and explain as the line imports the react library
into your file, interact projects import and interact is necessary because it provides a core
functionality for building user interfaces with components, even some new versions. So by
import this react library, you access the features, again access to the features and etc.
So and you can also explain what is the export default. I don't know. The price export
default is part of the JavaScript model system and it's used to specify the main value of the function
as it is model export. When you do it, you can also import this model from another file like
there's some explanation you can read like to not go into the documentation.
Okay, we can close it. The next quick action you can use is fix coding errors.
You have few options how to do it. For example, for example, let me think how we can do it.
Imagine we get to close the text and we have it. So we can close the hover on a problematic
zone. For example, when the compiler or yes, leaned argue about it, we hover and we have an option
fix using the pilot. And you see the pilot just added the close tag. For example, we can do it
the next way. We can select the code. We can do the right click, compile it, fix, and compile it
to do the same. It will fix the value. Also, like we have same with the React. React is
declared but it's very similar to we can do the quick fix. But it's not compiler to just
remove us import of React because we don't really use it. So it's a VS code also to do some
suggestions. The next quick action is reviewing the code. We can select the code. We're interested
to get some recommendations. We can do the right click, compile it, and review and comment.
Let's see. That was the problem with rename it to button text in the distracting which may
cause confusion. Consider using the name and for quality. Okay, so we see the renaming as a runway.
So let's fix it. We just applied the button text with not renaming the variable.
Next, it suggests us to do some documentation but we don't want to do it so we will discard it.
Okay, so you can get some recommendations for your code from compile it. As the next quick action,
you can use generate documentation. For example, you can do the right click in your code.
Just compile it and generate docs.
It will generate some just documentation like explaining, okay, what is the props? What is the
props on the button text? It's the text to display inside the button. We also have
a retooling the J6 element. We can also accept it. So I will call this more documented now.
Okay, we can also generate some tests using compile it. We can generate tests for the whole
of the file or select some specific parts but we don't really have any specific parts to select.
So it makes sense to generate it for the whole of the file. We click on generate tests.
When you seek a private created new file buttons dot test dot J6, we can close the chart
and we see it use some libraries, some tests and libraries for the components and provide us
three tests. We first check the render of the button with the given text, then passes additional
props to the button element and then close on click handle when click. You can apply it and it will
create the new button text dot dot test the J6 file. So what else you can do? You can fix also
terminal roles. Let's open a new terminal and for example imagine you want to use some command.
I don't know. Let's do a npm around that. So you see it doesn't work because I don't know why.
Yeah, imagine I don't know why it's the explanation of the terminal is too difficult to me. I can
click on a compiler then click on explain using compile it and it tells me it fails because there
is no packet adjacent file in your project. Okay, yeah, now it's clear to me or we can click
and fix using compile it. We want to suggest some commands we can use but because we don't have
packages on. So what we can do, we can create a new package, JSON file with default values.
We can do in payment style of some specific package. So we do some relevant suggestions for us.
Okay, I gonna close it. So now you know what locations are. So I went to use and I hope it was
useful to you and see you in the next lesson.